newszoom.com 2005-12-12

# NewsZoom.com Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**  
    NewsZoom is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site. In order to enhance your experience at our sites we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, zip code, and country. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our sites.   

    By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by NewsZoom as outlined in this privacy policy. NewsZoom does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third party unless specified.   
**IP address and logging**  

    Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).   
**Third Party Advertising**  

    We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit NewsZoom. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).   
**Cookies**  

    Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers.   
**Third Party Cookies**  

    In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.   
**Meta Search Engine**  

    It's very important to differentiate between two kinds of search engines;  
one is a database assisted search engine which is the case that one site have a database of LINKS and when a vistor searches it goes through the database and picks the proper results and display the results in the browser, the other one is a _meta search engine_ which is the case of NewsZoom that the site has NO database of links and NO other related content to the search results, but only crawls the internet and some news servers for obtaining headlines which are neither located in a database nor in our servers physically.   
**Disclaimer**  

    This is an information tool provided by at no charge to the user.   

    NewsZoom makes no warranties, expressed or implied, for the services we provide. NewsZoom will not be held responsible for any damages you or your business may suffer from using NewsZoom services. NewsZoom will not be held responsible for any interruptions, delays, failures, inaccuracies, or typographical errors.   
NewsZoom does not represent or warrant that the Service or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. NewsZoom does not warrant or represent that the use or the results of the use of the Service or the materials made available as part of the Service will be correct, accurate, timely, or otherwise reliable.   

    NewsZoom is collecting news headlines all over the internet. All these headlines and the content of the news page NewsZoom link to is NOT affiliated with NewsZoom and NewsZoom cannot be held responsible for the content of the news page it links to.   
**Liability**  

    It is NewsZoom's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, NewsZoom will immediately disable and remove content in question. 

To report illegal content please: 

Click Here

|
